Hi everyone and welcome to a new Paradise video.
And I just recorded a jumpsuit up video with this catsuit here, so I decided to just leave it on for the intro of this video.
I received the newest Paradise pants.
It's the black one without a zipper in the front.
So no sip paradise for leather leggings. And I also have new lingerie from the latest collection which I want to show you. Both is like black and nude but different types.
and a lot of lazy stuff so I think I'll start with the leggings and after that
the laundry I'm going to get changed first impression it fits so good it's
like the classic paradise fit just really good and I have to say I wasn't
short first because I'm so used to the zipper pants that I thought well am I
going to like it but I like it I think especially with this combination and
this bodysuit it looks really splendid
yeah back is like always with the seams here they said that they made the
waistline a bit wider so you can get into the pants without a zipper and don't get stuck or
something so I had no problems they're also super elastic and stretchy no worries I'm wearing size
small but as you just saw they're super stretchy and the fabric just looks so good I have my normal
aesthetic pants for like two years now and I had no problems with the fabric whatsoever
so I have high hopes that this one is going to stay with me for a while and I'm going to wear
them for sure what can I say it no surprise here it fits again it looks really good again
just what I'm used to from Paradise and you can also check out my other Paradise videos because
they have a lot of other colors and materials and I made a whole bunch of
videos about my paradise pants just searching on my channel. Alright now on to
the bras of the lingerie and we have again what I love here a no wire bra so really
comfortable and give me a sec I'll be back
No?
I don't know.
I'm back with the first lingerie set and Nono, she's visiting me again.
And I think she looks like a perfect match to this lingerie set.
And the shoes...
Get in some heels.
Hey
Checking out the set
this design is so cute with all the lace parts and
It is not see-through although it may look like it with the nude color everywhere, but totally safe
and I have to say that the bra is just so comfortable because
There are no wires and it's still a push-up bra
so you have the push-up effect and the highest comfort of wearing. I'm not going
to turn around you can see that on Patreon but what I love about the panties
and what is new is that they're kind of size adjustable here on the straps so
you have these little thingies and you can shorten or lengthen the straps here
so they're going to fit even better. Cat is sitting right there watching me so my
audience today. Oh, now she's yawning. Thank you. Anyway, this is the first set. I have a second set,
which is quite similar concerning the pattern, but it's just a bralette, so to say. I don't know,
because no padding, no wires, no push-up. I'm going to change into that one now. Second set.
and I have to say I already wore the bralette and also the push-up bra at work and stuff like that
and they're both really comfortable also I like the design with the lace here and it's
so comfortable because as I said no padding no wires just a bit of fabric and a bit of fabric
we have here as well although a bit more straps than with the first Pandy I think
I like this Pandy better because I like the design better and also again really
cool that I can adjust the straps and the length so yeah I like this set as
well pretty much I think they have the sets at least a push-up set also in red
You can check everything out on their homepage. I'll link of course everything
down below and I also have a discount code for Paradise. You can use it to get
10% off. It's Celine and I write everything down below under the video.
This is the end for this video. I hope you had fun. Tell me in the comments
which your favorite
lingerie set is
this one or the first one
I think I can't really decide
I love the
both of the bras and this panty
yeah I don't know
anyway have a nice time see ya
bye